chocolatechocolateandmore.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy - Chocolate Chocolate and More!

Your privacy is very important to us. We do not distribute your personal information to third parties for any purpose. We appreciate your business and are committed to protect your personal information as we would our own. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Chocolate, Chocolate and more website. On some pages you can comment and register to receive updates. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name  
Address  
Phone Number  
Email Address

### The Way We Use Information:

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our mailing list as well as updates and news. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form or check the appropriate box when placing an order.

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include saving your shopping cart information for a future visit or remembering your login status.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by visiting the My Account section of our website. You may log in to your account and view or modify your saved information. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
